Igor's final song, Are We Still Friends,
features a guitar solo from what famous
rock musician?
>> Check White.
>> Yeah,
>> come on.
>> That was too easy.
>> One of Tyler's favorite moments and my
favorite moments on Eigor is the bridge
on I think. There are a lot of versions
of I think as a bridge. Which number
version do we end up hearing?
>> I've definitely read this before, but I
don't know the exact number.
>> He tweeted out nine. So, this is like
the ninth version of the bridge.
>> Tyler wrote running out of time during a
recording session with what other
rapper? It's not Kanye.
>> No.
>> Give me a hint.
>> The rapper is from Harlem.
>> ASAP Ferg.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Asaf Ferg. When did Tyler have the
original idea for Gone Gone? What year?
>> 2013 Wolf Tour.
>> Yes. Damn. [laughter] I didn't even get
it.
>> Okay, so last one. Tyler said that the
minimalistic sound of Eigor was inspired
by something specific. I believe he went
to a friend's house and the only thing
in the house was like a couch and like
this super amazing artistic sound system
and I believe he said like we have so
much in our lives in our house that
we don't need and I wanted to kind of
make a record that was representative of
>> Damn Charles. Damn.
>> Come on. I love this [laughter] record
bro. Am I?